Jacob Todasco

Jacob T

Jake.todasco@live.com

7787514450 Surrey Canada

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

I am detail-oriented, inquisitive and organized in my work process. I see any task to completion and I do so to the best of my abilities. I have numerous years of customer service experience which has provided me with compassion, patience and the willingness to satisfy a potential customer. I invigorate my colleagues through humour and light-hearted discussions.

I've also 20 years of various computer experience including video and picture editing, document and spreadsheet usage, product inquiry, research and data entry.

I'm a 'Jake' of all trades, and a master of pun. I also dabble in comedy.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service | London Drugs | Surrey, BC | From Oct 2017 to present

I am the main aisle person in service of product management as well as a big emphasis on customer support.

Graveyard Stock | Home Depot | Surrey, Canada | From Aug 2016 to Apr 2017

Organized with a team to manage the incoming stock appropriately using mobile machinery and other necessary tools between the hours of 9pm and 5am.

Receiver | Home Outfitters | Burnaby, Canada | From Jun 2011 to Aug 2014

Day to day stock handler and shipper/receiver in charge of the incoming stock.

EDUCATION

Go Studios | https://gostudios.ca/ | Vancouver, Canada | From Sep 2014 to Feb 2015

Area of Study/Major: Acting for Television, Voice and Cinema

Each day in the week was something different, a wide array of skill focused classes related to acting such as voice work, improv, voice and movement, business, scene study, and script writing.

SKILLS

- · Paint.NET Proficiency: Proficient
- · Video Editing Video, Technical Proficiency: Proficient
- Computer Skills Office Assistance / Secretary Proficiency: Proficient
- Conflict Management People skills Proficiency: Basic Knowledge
- Positive Attitude Traits (Enablers or Disablers) Proficiency: Expert
- Taking Responsibility Traits (Enablers or Disablers) Proficiency: Expert
- Motivating people People related Skills Proficiency: Basic Knowledge
- Comedy / Humor Books Writing Proficiency: Basic Knowledge

LANGUAGES

• English Proficiency: Fluent

JOB SEARCH DETAILS

Categories of Interest:
Data Entry, Entertainment & Media, Human Services, Internet & Ecommerce, Online Marketing

• Job Types: Employee, Freelance, Temporary

Schedules: Flexible Schedule
Level of Remote Work: 100% Remote Work

Start Date: Immediately
Availability: Flexible
Maximum Hours/Week: Flexible

Flexible Schedule, Remote Work, Freelancing Job • Job Flexibility Preferences:

• Career Level:

Entry-Level High School Degree • Highest Education Level: